A Guide to the American Conservation Association (ACA) records FA475
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Files, 1921, 1928, 1932, 1938, 1943, 1952, 1955-2009; 2; 53.68 box(es) Boxes 39-180, 1 small artifact box
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2002, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 795)
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 796)
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 797)
  - Environmental Advocates of New York, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 798)
  - Environmental Bond Act, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 799)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, 1970-1972, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 801)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, 1985, 1987-1991 (Box 83, Folder 804)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 806)
  - Enviromnental Law Institute, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 808)
  - Environmental Law Institute, 1987-1990 (Box 84, Folder 810)
  - Environmental Media Services, 2005-2006 (Box 84, Folder 811)
  - Enviromnental Planning Lobby (EPL Institute, Incorporated), 1984-1986 (Box 84, Folder 812)
  - Enviromnental Policy Institute, 1984-1986 (Box 84, Folder 813)
  - Environmental Policy Institute, 1986-1988 (Box 85, Folder 814-815)
  - Environmental Priorities, 1976-1981 (Box 85, Folder 819-820)
  - Environmental Priorities, Minutes of Meetings, 1978-1981 (Box 86, Folder 821-822)
  - Environmental Priorities, Minutes of Meetings, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 823)
  - Environmental Priorities, Reports, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 824)
  - Environmental Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 826)
  - Environmental Teach-In, Incorporated, 1969-1970 (Box 86, Folder 827)
  - Environmental Television Institute, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 828)
  - Environmental Working Group, 2008 (Box 86, Folder 829)
  - Fa-Fl, 1972-1980, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 831)
  - Fo, 1969-1970, 1972-1973, 1975-1981, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 832)
  - Fr, 1972-1977 (Box 87, Folder 833)
  - Fu, 1972-1973, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 834)
  - Federated Conservationists of Westchester County, Incorporated, 1967, 1970, 1976-1981 (Box 87, Folder 836)
  - Federated Conservationists of Westchester County, Incorporated, 1968, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 837)
  - Federated Conservationists of Westchester County, Incorporated, 1980-1982 (Box 87, Folder 838)
  - Federation of New York State Bird Clubs, Incorporated, 1968 1980-1982, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 839)
  - Forer, Lois G., 1964 (Box 87, Folder 840)
  - Foresight Films, 1981-1985, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 841)
  - Forest History Society, Incorporated, 1959-1965, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 842)
  - Forest History Society, Incorporated, 1969, 1971-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 88, Folder 843)
  - Foresta Institute for Ocean and Mountain Studies, 1967, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 845)
  - Foundation of America, 1964-1965 (Box 88, Folder 846)
  - The Fresh Air Fund, 1970, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 847)
  - Friends of the Animals, Incorporated, 1974, 1978-1979, 1991, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 849)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1995-1996 (Box 89, Folder 852)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 853)
  - Friends of the Earth, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 854)
  - Friends of the Earth Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 89, Folder 856)
  - Friends of the Earth Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 89, Folder 857)
  - Friends of the Earth Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 89, Folder 858)
  - Friends of Shawangunks, 1990-1991 (Box 89, Folder 859)
  - Ga-Gl, 1965, 1970, 1972-1974, 1976-1980, 1987-1988, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 860)
  - Gr-Gu, 1972-1975, 1977-1980, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 861)
  - Girl Scouts of the United States of America, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder 863)
  - Grand Canyon Trust, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 90, Folder 865)
  - Green Guide Institute, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 867)
  - Green Seal, 1991-1993 (Box 90, Folder 868)
  - Greenfield, New York, 1978, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 871)
  - Greer Children's Community, 1967-1969 (Box 91, Folder 872)
  - Gregg, Frank, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 873)
  - Harlem River/ New York University (NYU), 1965-1968 (Box 91, Folder 878)
  - Harlem River/New York University (NYU), Printed Material, 1952, 1955, 1963-1966 (Box 92, Folder 879-881)
  - Harvard University, John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1987-1988 (Box 92, Folder 882)
  - Helm, Shapiro, Ayers and Aldrich, P.C., 1975-1976 (Box 92, Folder 883)
  - Historical Society of Martinique, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 884)
  - Hudson River Valley Greenway Council, 1988-1989 (Box 92, Folder 885)
  - Human Environment Center, 1980-1981 (Box 92, Folder 886)
  - Human Environment Center, 1982-1984 (Box 92, Folder 887)
  - Inform, 1977-1978 (Box 93, Folder 891)
  - Inform, 1987-1990 (Box 93, Folder 893)
  - Institute of Man and Science, 1964-1965, 1968, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 901-902)
  - Institute of Northern Agricultural Research, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 904)
  - International Committee on National Parks, Budget, 1960-1963, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 905-906)
  - International Committee on National Parks, Congo Park, 1961-1963, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 907)
  - International Committee on National Parks, General Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 95, Folder 909)
  - International Committee on National Parks, Printed Material, 1961-1962, 1975-1970 (Box 96, Folder 910-911)
  - International Council for Bird Preservation/ United States Section, Incorporated, 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 913)
  - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Resources (IUCN), 1971-1975 (Box 97, Folder 918)
  - Island Resources Foundation, 1972-1973, 1975-1980 (Box 97, Folder 923)
  - Island Resources Foundation, "Foxfire" Project, 1970, 1972-1976 (Box 98, Folder 928-930)
  - Jackson Hole Alliance for Responsible Planning, 1986-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 99, Folder 932)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (LBJ), "A More Beautiful America", Book, 1964-1967 (Box 99, Folder 933-934)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 1998-2000 (Box 99, Folder 939)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 1998-1999 (Box 99, Folder 940)
    Formerly National Wildflower Research Center (WNRC)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 941)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2000-2002 (Box 99, Folder 942)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2000-2002 (Box 99, Folder 943)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2002-2004 (Box 100, Folder 945)
  - Lady Bird Johnson Wildflower Center, 2005-2006 (Box 100, Folder 947)
  - Lake Champlain Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 100, Folder 950)
  - Land and Water Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 100, Folder 952)
  - Land and Water Fund, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 953)
  - Land and Water Fund Project, 1995-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 100, Folder 954)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1991-1995 (Box 100, Folder 957-958)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1991, 1998-2000 (Box 101, Folder 960)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 961)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1996-1997 (Box 101, Folder 962)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1997-1998 (Box 101, Folder 963)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 1998-1999 (Box 101, Folder 964)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 2000-2001 (Box 101, Folder 965)
  - The Land Trust Alliance, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 966)
  - Land Trust Exchange, 1984-1990 (Box 101, Folder 973)
  - Landscape Architecture Foundation, 1982, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 976)
  - LBJ Memorial Grove on the Potomac, Society for a More Beautiful National Capital, Incorporated, 1972, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 977)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 981)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 102, Folder 982)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 1998-1999 (Box 102, Folder 983)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 102, Folder 984)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 102, Folder 985)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 102, Folder 986)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 2001-2004 (Box 102, Folder 987)
  - League of Conservation Voters Education Fund, 2003-2004 (Box 102, Folder 989)
  - League of Women Voters Educational Fund, 1962-1963, 1966-1971 (Box 103, Folder 994-996)
  - Lighthawk, The Wings of Conservation, 1983, 1987-1990 (Box 103, Folder 997)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1971, 1995-1997 (Box 104, Folder 1003)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 1004)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 1005)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 1998, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 1006)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 1008)
  - Manomet Bird Observatory, 1968-1971 (Box 104, Folder 1014)
  - Manomet Bird Observatory, 1969, 1972-1975 (Box 105, Folder 1015)
  - Manomet Bird Observatory, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 105, Folder 1016)
  - Marincello Project, California, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 1017)
  - Marine Research Foundation, 1954, 1960-1964 (Box 105, Folder 1018)
  - Marine Research Foundation, Carl O. Gustafson, Shellfish Culture Study, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1019)
  - Mariposa County, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1020)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1969-1971 (Box 105, Folder 1021-1022)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1970-1974 (Box 105, Folder 1023)
  - The Meditation Institute, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 1024)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1987-1991 (Box 105, Folder 1025)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1988, 1993-1996 (Box 106, Folder 1028)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1029-1030)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1993, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 1035)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1993, 1998-2000 (Box 107, Folder 1036)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 1037)
  - Mineral Policy Center, 2003 (Box 107, Folder 1039)
  - Mohonk Preserve, Incorproated, 1881-1982, 1985-1986 (Box 107, Folder 1040)
  - Montana Land Reliance, 1987-1989 (Box 107, Folder 1041)
  - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet, 1995-1996 (Box 107, Folder 1043)
  - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet, 1996-1997 (Box 107, Folder 1045)
  - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet, 1997 (Box 107, Folder 1046)
  - Mothers and Others for a Livable Planet, 1998-2000 (Box 107, Folder 1048)
  - John Muir Institute for Environmental Studies, Incorporated, 1968, 1973, 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 108, Folder 1050-1052)
  - John Muir Institute for Environmental Studies, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 108, Folder 1053)
  - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1971, 1977, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1054)
  - Nas-National Committee for Citizens in Education, 1972-1975, 1978-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1055)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1970-1972 (Box 110, Folder 1065)
  - National Audubon Society, 1960-1961, 1965-1966, 1968-1971 (Box 110, Folder 1066)
  - National Audubon Society, 1970, 1977-1981 (Box 110, Folder 1067)
  - National Audubon Society, 1981, 1991-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1068-1069)
  - National Audubon Society, 1982, 1984, 1986 (Box 111, Folder 1074)
  - National Audubon Society, 1994, 1996 (Box 112, Folder 1077)
  - National Audubon Society, 1998-1999 (Box 112, Folder 1080)
  - National Audubon Society, 1999-2000 (Box 112, Folder 1081)
  - National Audubon Society, 2000-2002 (Box 112, Folder 1082)
  - National Audubon Society, 2001-2002 (Box 112, Folder 1083)
  - National Audubon Society, 2004 (Box 112, Folder 1085)
  - National Capital Planning Commission, 1967 (Box 112, Folder 1091)
  - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation, 1963 (Box 112, Folder 1093)
  - National Council of State Garden Clubs, Incorporated, 1964-1965 (Box 112, Folder 1094-1095)
  - National Council of State Garden Clubs, Incorporated, Material Used, Etc., 1964-1965 (Box 113, Folder 1098-1099)
  - National Council of State Garden Clubs, Incorporated, Reservations, Etc., 1964-1965 (Box 113, Folder 1100-1101)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 114, Folder 1104-1106)
  - National Institute for Urban Wildlife, 1974, 1982-1986 (Box 114, Folder 1107-1108)
  - National Maritime Historical Society, 1973, 1980-1981 (Box 115, Folder 1110)
  - National Park Foundation, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 115, Folder 1112)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1980-1981 (Box 116, Folder 1121)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1982-1986 (Box 116, Folder 1122)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1986-1991 (Box 116, Folder 1123-1126)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1991-1995 (Box 117, Folder 1129)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1995-1996 (Box 117, Folder 1131)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1998 (Box 117, Folder 1133)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 1999-2000 (Box 117, Folder 1134)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 2000-2001 (Box 117, Folder 1135)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 2001-2002 (Box 117, Folder 1136)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association, 2003-2004 (Box 117, Folder 1138)
  - National Planning Association, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 1143)
  - National Recreation and Park Association, 1965 (Box 117, Folder 1144)
  - National Recreation and Park Association, Citizens Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality, 1971-1976 (Box 118, Folder 1147)
  - National Recreation Association, 1960-1962 (Box 118, Folder 1149)
  - National Roadside Council (Proposed), 1963-1965 (Box 118, Folder 1150)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 1151)
  - National Wildflower Research Center, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 118, Folder 1153)
  - National Wildflower Research Center, 1987-1991 (Box 118, Folder 1154)
  - National Wildflower Research Center, 1991-1995 (Box 118, Folder 1155)
  - National Wildflower Research Center, 1995-1996 (Box 118, Folder 1156)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1943, 1970, 1981-1986 (Box 118, Folder 1159)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1987-1991 (Box 119, Folder 1161-1165)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1991-1995 (Box 119, Folder 1166)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1995-1996 (Box 120, Folder 1168)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1997-1999 (Box 120, Folder 1171)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1999-2000 (Box 120, Folder 1172)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 2000-2001 (Box 120, Folder 1173)
  - National Youth Conference on Natural Beauty and Conservation, 1955-1968 (Box 120, Folder 1177)
  - National Youth Conference on Natural Beauty and Conservation, Printed Material, 1966-1969 (Box 120, Folder 1178)
  - Natural Area Council, Incorporated, 1972, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 1182)
  - Natural Beauty Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 121, Folder 1183)
  - Natural History Museum of the Adirondacks, 1999, 2001 (Box 121, Folder 1186)
  - Natural Resources Council of America, 1962-1964, 1966-1971 (Box 122, Folder 1188-1189)
  - Natural Resources Council of America, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 1190)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1973-1975 (Box 123, Folder 1197-1198)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1975-1976 ,1978, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 1199)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1981-1985 (Box 124, Folder 1202-1204)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1985-1986 (Box 124, Folder 1205)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1988-1991 (Box 125, Folder 1209-1210)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1991-1995 (Box 125, Folder 1211)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1995-1996 (Box 126, Folder 1213)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1998-1999 (Box 126, Folder 1216)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 1999-2000 (Box 126, Folder 1217)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2000-2001 (Box 126, Folder 1218)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2001-2002 (Box 126, Folder 1219)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 1221)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1962-1965, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 1228)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1983, 1986-1991 (Box 127, Folder 1235)
  - The Nature Conservancy, 1991-1993 (Box 127, Folder 1236)
  - Nature Conservancy of Hawaii, 1983, 1987-1991 (Box 128, Folder 1240)
  - New England Forestry Foundation, 1963-1964, 1967, 1969-1970 (Box 128, Folder 1241)
  - New Renaissance Center, 1987-1988, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 1243-1244)
  - New York City, Council on the Environment of New York City, 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 1246)
  - New York City, Park Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 128, Folder 1247)
  - New York Conservation Council and American Game Association Foundation, 1975 (Box 129, Folder 1249)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 1994 (Box 129, Folder 1250)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 1994-1996 (Box 129, Folder 1251)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 129, Folder 1251)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 129, Folder 1252)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 1999-2000 (Box 129, Folder 1254)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 129, Folder 1255)
  - New York Conservation Education Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 129, Folder 1256)
  - New York Environmental Institute, Incorporated, 1985, 1987-1991 (Box 129, Folder 1257)
  - New York Environmental Institute, Incorporated, 1985, 1991-1995 (Box 129, Folder 1258)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1988-1991 (Box 129, Folder 1263)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1991-1995 (Box 129, Folder 1264)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1994-1996 (Box 130, Folder 1267)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1995-1997 (Box 130, Folder 1268)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1997-1998 (Box 130, Folder 1270)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1998-1999 (Box 130, Folder 1271)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 1999-2000 (Box 130, Folder 1272)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 2000-2001 (Box 130, Folder 1273)
  - New York Parks and Conservation Association, 2001-2003 (Box 130, Folder 1274)
  - New York State, Adirondack Park Agency, 1980-1981 (Box 131, Folder 1277)
  - New York State, Conservation Department- Booz, Allen, and Hamilton Study, 1966-1967, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 1278-1282)
  - New York State, Department of Environmental Conservation, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 1283)
  - New York State, Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, 1966 (Box 131, Folder 1284)
  - New York State, Historic Trust, 1969-1970 (Box 131, Folder 1285)
  - New York State, Natural Heritage Trust, 1968-1975, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 1286)
  - New York State, Natural Heritage Trust, 1970-1971 (Box 132, Folder 1288)
  - New York State, Natural Heritage Trust, 1989-1990 (Box 132, Folder 1290)
  - New York State, Recreation Council Advisory Committee, 1965 (Box 132, Folder 1291)
  - New York State, Temporary Study Commission on the Future of the Adirondacks, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 1292)
  - New York State Environmental Project, 2000 (Box 132, Folder 1293)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1976, 1976-1991 (Box 132, Folder 1294)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 1991-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 132, Folder 1295)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 1992-1994 (Box 133, Folder 1296-1297)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 1995-1997 (Box 133, Folder 1298)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 1996-1997 (Box 133, Folder 1299)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 1997-1998 (Box 133, Folder 1300)
  - New York Zoological Society/The Wildlife Conservation Society, 2000-2001 (Box 133, Folder 1301)
  - New York-New Jersey Trail Conference, 1980-1982 (Box 133, Folder 1302)
  - New York-New Jersey Trail Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 133, Folder 1303)
  - Northeast New York Public Telecommunication Council, Incorporated, 1984-1986 (Box 133, Folder 1304)
  - Northern Rockies Action Group, 1975, 1987-1991 (Box 133, Folder 1307)
  - Northern Rockies Action Group, 1991-1993 (Box 134, Folder 1308)
  - 1000 Friends of Florida, 1988-1991 (Box 134, Folder 1310-1312)
  - 1000 Friends of Florida, 1990-1993 (Box 134, Folder 1313-1314)
  - 1000 Friends of Oregon, 1985-1991 (Box 135, Folder 1315-1316)
  - 1000 Friends of Oregon, 1990-1993 (Box 135, Folder 1317-1318)
  - Open Space Institute, 1983-1985 (Box 135, Folder 1320-1321)
  - Open Space Institute, 1988-1991 (Box 135, Folder 1322)
  - Open Space Institute, 1991-1995 (Box 136, Folder 1324-1325)
  - Open Space Institute, 1995-1996 (Box 136, Folder 1326)
  - Open Space Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 136, Folder 1327)
  - Open Space Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 136, Folder 1328)
  - Open Space Institute, 1997-1999 (Box 136, Folder 1329)
  - Open Space Institute, 1998-2000 (Box 136, Folder 1330)
  - Open Space Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 136, Folder 1331)
  - Open Space Institute, 2001-2002 (Box 136, Folder 1332)
  - Open Space Institute, 2003-2004 (Box 136, Folder 1333)
  - Open Space Institute, Sterling Forest Project, 1993-1994 (Box 136, Folder 1338)
  - Pace University, Pace Environmental Law Center, 1949, 1971, 1975, 1998-1999 (Box 137, Folder 1344)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1975-1977 (Box 137, Folder 1345)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1982, 1986 (Box 137, Folder 1346)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Hudson River Valley Commission, 1965-1966 (Box 137, Folder 1348)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Iona Island Study, 1964 (Box 137, Folder 1349)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission, Youth Employment Program, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 1351)
  - Pan American Development Foundation, Incorporated, Vicuna Reserve, 1965, 1969-1970 (Box 137, Folder 1352)
  - Park Association of New York City, Incorporated, 1967-1971 (Box 138, Folder 1353)
  - Park Facilities, 1971 (Box 138, Folder 1354)
  - Parks Council, 1971-1972 (Box 138, Folder 1359)
  - Partnership for Community Building, 2001-2002 (Box 138, Folder 1362)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1984-1987 (Box 138, Folder 1363)
  - Pennsylannia Academy of Fine Arts, Publicly Owned Bronze Sculpture in Outdoor Settings, 1984-1989 (Box 138, Folder 1364-1366)
  - Philadelphia Conservationists, Incorporated, 1965-1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 139, Folder 1372)
  - Planet Live: Countdown 2000, Incorporated, 1991-1993 (Box 139, Folder 1373)
  - Population Project, 1991-1992 (Box 139, Folder 1374)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1976, 1978-1979 (Box 139, Folder 1376)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 1377)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1987, 1991-1993 (Box 140, Folder 1378)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1987-1991 (Box 140, Folder 1379-1381)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1995-1996 (Box 140, Folder 1382)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1996-1997 (Box 140, Folder 1383)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1997-1998 (Box 140, Folder 1384)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1998-1999 (Box 140, Folder 1385)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 1999-2000 (Box 140, Folder 1386)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 2000-2001 (Box 140, Folder 1387)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 2001-2002 (Box 140, Folder 1388)
  - Project for Public Spaces, Incorporated, 2003-2004 (Box 140, Folder 1390)
  - Prospect Park, Centennial Committee, 1966 (Box 140, Folder 1394)
  - Public Affairs Committee, Incorpoated, 1966-1969 (Box 141, Folder 1395)
  - Public Lands Institute, 1977-1980 (Box 141, Folder 1396)
  - Public Voice for Food and Health Policy, Incorporated, National Association of Farmers' Market Nutrition Programs (NAFMNP), Urban Project, 1997 (Box 141, Folder 1397)
  - Public Voice for Food and Health Policy, Incorporated, re: National Association of Farmers' Market Nutrition Programs (NAFMNP), 1998 (Box 141, Folder 1398)
  - Quebec-Labrador Foundation, Atlantic Center for the Environment, 1975, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 141, Folder 1401)
  - Rachel's Network, 2001-2002 (Box 141, Folder 1403)
  - Rails-to-Trails Conservancy, 1986-1991 (Box 141, Folder 1404)
  - Rails-to-Trails Conservancy, 1990-1996 (Box 142, Folder 1409-1410)